let quiz   =[
    {question: "The distance of the plane 2x-3y+6z+7=0 from the point (2,-3,-1) is ",
option:[
    4,
    3,
    2,
    5,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "The probability of an event is 3/7. Then odd against the event is" ,
option:[
    "4:3",
    "7:3",
    "3:7",
    "3:4",
],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The direction cosines of the y-axis are",
option:[
    "(6,0,0)",
    "(1,0,0)",
    "(0,1,0)",
    "(0,0,1)",


],
answer:3, 
},
{question: "A pair of dice are rolled. The probability of obtaining an even prime number on each die is",
option:[
    "1/12",
    "1/36",
    "1/6",
    "0",

],
answer:2, 
},

{
    question: "What is the integration of 1dx ",
option:[
    "x+c",
    0,
    "1+c",
    "2x+c",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Which of the following functions is decreasing on (0,pi/2)",
option:[
    "sin 2x",
    "tan x",
    "cos x",
    "cos 3x",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "The function F(x)=tan x - x",
option:[
    "Always increase",
    "Always decreases",
    "Sometimes increase and sometimes decreases",
    "Never increase",


],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The maximum value of sin x.cos x is" ,
option:[
    "1/4",
    "1/2",
    "3/4",
    "3/2",


],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "Let F: R->R be defined by F(x) = 2x + cos x,then F ",
option:[
    "is an increasing function",
    "is a decreasing function",
    "has a minimum at x=3t",
    "has a maximum at x=0",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Total number of possible matrices of order 3X3 with each entry 2 or 0 is",
option:[
    9,
    27,
    81,
    512,

    
],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "If A and B are two matrices of the order 3Xm and 3Xn, respectively, and m=n, then the order of matrix (5A-2B) is",
option:[
    "mX3",
    "3X3",
    "mXn",
    "3Xn",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "The set of points where the function f given by f(x) = |2x-1| sin x is differentiable is",
option:[
    "R",
    "R={1/2}",
    "(0,Infinity)",
    "None of these",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "The area of a triangle with vertices (-3,0),(3,0) and (0,k) is 9sq. units. The value of k will be ",
option:[
    9,
    3,
    -9,
    6,



],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "If A and B are square matrices then(AB)'",
option:[
    "B'A'",
    "A'B'",
    "AB'",    
    "A'B'",

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "If a matrix is both symmetric matrix and skew symmetric matrix",
option:[
    "Diagonal matrix",
    "Zero matrix",
    "Scalar matrix",
    "None of these",

],
answer:2, 
}]
